IAIN FLYNN

Apartment 26, The Vibe,

175 Broughton Lane, Salford, M7 1UD

Email: iain.flynn@me.com

PROFILE

I am a full stack .NET developer with 7+ years of commercial development experience across the full software development lifecycle. I have a deep interest in computing and enjoy tackling new challenges, and am always willing to broaden my horizons and learn to use new languages and technologies.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Framework .NET Java (including Servlets, JSP, JSF)

Database SQL Server, T-SQL Oracle, JDBC, MySQL

ORM Entity Framework

Web Technologies ASP.NET MVC & Webforms, PHP, Google Web Toolkit/App Engine

HTML5, CSS3, AJAX, JQuery

Programming languages C#, Javascript Python, VBScript, Java

EDUCATION

University of Manchester 2007-2011

MSc Advanced Computer Science Merit with honours

BSc Internet Computing First class with honours

Bury College 1999-2005

BTEC National Diploma for IT Practitioners

Triple Distinction

Other: ITIL Foundation level, Microsoft Office 2010 Master

EMPLOYMENT

GREAT PLACES HOUSING GROUP

APR 2014 - PRESENT

.NET Developer

- Developing in-house web-based CRM and Property Repair Management software used daily by hundreds of staff, including helpdesk support, maintenance operatives, and management
- Working as part of a development team that works closely with business analysis and technical application teams to deliver reliable solutions with an emphasis on code quality and meeting our company's requirements

PANNONE LLP

OCT 2012 - MAR 2014

Business Systems Developer

- Developing business-specific IT systems using .NET 4.5, ASP.NET MVC 4, C#, SQL Server, Entity Framework 4.5, WCF
- Working within a Scrum team to build a large application to log insurance claims and provide a centralised framework for future projects
- Rationalising future project development into central libraries, rewriting legacy applications

WEB APPLICATIONS UK

SEP 2011 - APR 2012

Web Developer

- Web development on travel software
- Involvement in the full development cycle, from new development tasks, through architecture, development, delivery and end user support for a wide spectrum of clients.

REFEREES

Human Resources

hr@greatplaces.org.uk

Great Places Housing Group 2A Derwent Avenue Manchester M21 7QP

Dr Bijan Parsia

Senior Lecturer bijan.parsia@manchester.ac.uk

Kilburn Building-2.32 School of Computer Science The University of Manchester Manchester M13 9PL